{
    "id": "b3c7dc709ab84320bcf62d78ff1d9b74",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was deaf ………………….. our requests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Regular exercise is beneficial ………………….. physical and mental health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you conscious ....................... your responsibilities?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We regret that we cannot comply ..................... your request.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The honor was conferred .....................… him at the convocation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He congratulated her ...................... her success.",
            "description": "Either on or for is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is thoroughly conversant ..................... . the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The principal has called ........................ an explanation from the students who boycotted their classes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t care ....................... your objections: I have decided to do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "about",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He fell ..................... . the displeasure of authorities.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "off",
                "under"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}